Guide to the Mathew B. Brady and Levin Corbin Handy Photographic Studios Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Mathew B. Brady Studio, circa 1860-1885; Series I; (18 boxes)
  - Albumen Photographic Prints, Unmounted, (223 photographic prints)
    - Unidentified locations
      - Soldiers gathered at a building near an ambrotype and photographic studio (Box 9, Folder 436)
      - Soldiers on a parade ground in camp (Box 9, Folder 437)
      - Steamboat (Box 9, Folder 438)
      - Steamboat gunboat, probably on Acquia Creek (Box 9, Folder 439)
      - Swamp (Box 9, Folder 440-441)
      - Two steamboats near shore, as well as two sailing ships (Box 9, Folder 442)
      - USS Montauk (Box 9, Folder 443)
      - USS Saugus (Box 9, Folder 444)
      - Winter quarters. A group of small wooden buildings (Box 9, Folder 445)
    - Exterior portraits at unidentified locations
      Arranged alphabetically by surname followed by unidentified groups arranged alphabetically by description.
      - Alexander, Thomas, and another officer in camp (Box 9, Folder 446)
      - Barlow, Francis Channing (Box 9, Folder 447)
      - Davis, Jefferson Columbus, and his staff (Box 9, Folder 448)
        Davis is second from right in first row
      - Potter, Robert Brown, and his staff, as well as Mathew Brady at the extreme right (Box 9, Folder 449)
      - Sedgwick, John, and his staff (Box 9, Folder 450)
      - Sheridan, Philip Henry (Box 9, Folder 451)
      - 44th Indiana Infantry, Company H (Box 9, Folder 452)
      - Calvary officers in winter quarters (Box 9, Folder 453)
      - Five soldiers (Box 9, Folder 454)
      - Four naval officers posed sitting on the deck of a ship (Box 9, Folder 455)
      - Four soldiers in camp (Box 9, Folder 456)
        Man on extreme right is probably Ambrose Burnside
      - Four soldiers posed sitting on chairs in camp (Box 9, Folder 457)
      - Group of soldiers (Box 9, Folder 458)
        Possibly the 44th Indiana Infantry at the Battle of Shiloh, Hardin County, Tennessee
      - Group of soldiers, (2 photographic prints) (Box 9, Folder 459)
        Misidentified as General Nightingale
      - Gun squad on deck of a monitor, (2 photographic prints) (Box 9, Folder 460)
      - Nine men and a drummer boy (Box 9, Folder 461)
        Possibly a group from the 22nd New York State Volunteers
      - Nine soldiers gathered around their winter quarters, "Pine Cottage" (Box 9, Folder 462)
      - Officers and sailors aboard the USS Colorado (Box 9, Folder 463)
      - Officers aboard the USS Mahopac (Box 9, Folder 464)
      - Officers posed standing (Box 9, Folder 465)
        Possibly the headquarters of Rufus King in Chattanooga, Tennessee
      - Party in camp (Box 9, Folder 466)
      - Religious service in a camp (Box 9, Folder 467)
      - Soldier with a long grey beard sitting on rocks (Box 9, Folder 468)
      - Soldiers (Box 9, Folder 469)
        Possibly a New York engineers battalion
      - Soldiers, wooded landscape (Box 9, Folder 470)
      - Ten soldiers (Box 9, Folder 471)
        Possibly members of a 4th regiment
      - Three men in camp, two in conversation (Box 9, Folder 472)
      - Three men in front of a tent emblazoned with "Head Quarters" (Box 9, Folder 473)
      - Three officers and a drum corps (Box 9, Folder 474)
      - Two soldiers posed standing in front of a log building (Box 9, Folder 475)
      - Two soldiers sitting underneath a tent and an African American man posed standing with a horse in camp (Box 9, Folder 476)
      - Union sailors aboard the Confederate ram,CSS Albemarle (Box 9, Folder 477)
    - Studio portraits
      - Bartlett, William Chambers (Box 9, Folder 478)
      - Booth, John Wilkes (Box 9, Folder 479)
      - Hollins, George Nichols, Confederate States of America Navy (Box 9, Folder 480)
      - Lincoln, Abraham (Box 9, Folder 481)
      - Meade, George Gordon, and his staff (Box 9, Folder 482)
      - Steuart, George Hume, Confederate States of America (Box 9, Folder 483)
    - Copy photographs of studio portraits
      - Banks, Nathaniel Prentice, and his staff (Box 9, Folder 484)
      - Brown, Harvey (Box 9, Folder 485)
      - Henderson, Robert Miller (Box 9, Folder 486)
      - Kellogg, John Azor, and his staff (Box 9, Folder 487)
      - McKean, Thomas Jefferson, and his staff (Box 9, Folder 488)
      - Nagle, James,and others (Box 9, Folder 489)
        Engraving
      - Richardson, Israel Bush, and his staff (Box 9, Folder 490)
      - Rodenbough, Theophilus Francis (Box 9, Folder 491)
      - Wallen, Henry Davis (Box 9, Folder 492)
      - Officers from the 4th Army Corps (Box 9, Folder 493)
      - Man (Box 9, Folder 494)
  - Oversize, Multiple Photographic Prints Mounted on Blue Board, 170 photographic prints on 32 boards
    Multiple albumen photographic prints of studio portraits mounted on blue cardboard that depict officers in the United States military, except where noted., circa 1860-1865.
    Individual card mounts arranged by mount number, which range from 1 to 43, followed by four unnumbered mounts. Photographic prints on each card are expressed in the order they appear on the card from left to right and top to bottom.
    - Card No. 1, (4 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 495)
      - R. P. Barry, 16th United States Infantry
      - Francis M. Bache, 16th United States Infantry
      - William Wood, 17th United States Infantry
      - N. Prine, 17th United States Infantry
    - Card No. 4, (5 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 496)
      - James McQuade, 14th New York Infantry
      - Oliver L. Terry, 13th New York Infantry
      - Charles Adams Johnson, 17th New York Infantry
      - William B. Crandall, 16th New York Infantry
      - Henry S. Lansing, 17th New York Infantry
    - Card No. 7, (6 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 497)
      - Albert H. Jameson, 32nd Pennsylvania Infantry (3rd Pennsylvania Reserve Infantry)
      - 33rd Pennsylvania Infantry, Company B
      - George Dare, 34th Pennsylvania Infantry (5th Pennsylvania Reserve Infantry)
      - William Sinclair, 35th Pennsylvania Infantry (6th Regiment, Pennsylvania Reserve Infantry)
      - S. M. Bailey, 37th Pennsylvania Infantry (8th Regiment, Pennsylvania Reserve Infantry)
      - John S. McCalmont, 39th Pennsylvania Infantry (10th Regiment, Pennsylvania Reserve Infantry)
    - Card No. 8, (4 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 498)
      - Captain Isaac D. Derussy, 1st United States Infantry
      - Sidney Burbank, 2nd United States Infantry
      - Benjamin Louis Eulalie de Bonneville, 3rd United States Infantry
      - T. Morris, 4th United States Infantry
    - Card No. 9, (4 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 499)
      - Unidentified man
      - Samuel A Duncan, 4th United States Colored Troops
      - Samuel Chapman Armstrong, 8th United States Colored Troops and the founder of the Hampton Institute
      - Albert M. Blackman, 27th United States Colored Troops
    - Card No. 10, (4 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 500)
      - George Von Amsberg, 45th New York Infantry
      - H. Brandenstein, 46th New York Infantry
      - William B. Barton, 48th New York Infantry
      - James H. Perry and Daniel D. Bidwell, 49th N.Y. Infantry
    - Card No. 11, (6 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 501)
      - G. Bourri, 68th New York Infantry
      - Robert J. Betge, 68th New York Infantry
      - Albert Von Steinhausen, 68th New York Infantry
      - Carl Von Wedell, 68th New York Infantry
      - Robert Nugent, 69th New York Infantry
      - James Bagley, 69th New York Infantry
    - Card No. 14, (6 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 502)
      - Nelson Taylor, 72nd New York Infantry
      - William Oliver Stevens, 72nd New York Infantry, (2 photographic prints)
      - Dr. C. K. Irvine, 72nd New York Infantry
      - William Root Brewster, 72nd New York Infantry
      - John A. Dodge, 75th New York Infantry
    - Card No. 15, (3 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 503)
      - Stephen Joseph McGroarty, 82nd Ohio Infantry
      - Charles Candy, 66th Ohio Infantry
      - Samuel H. Hunt, 144th Ohio Infantry
    - Card No. 16, (7 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 504)
      - Edward J. Riley, 40th New York Infantry
      - James E. Dexter, 40th New York Infantry
      - Leopold Von Gilsa, 41st New York Infantry
      - Adolphus Weiss, 41st New York Infantry
      - James E. Mallon, 42nd New York Infantry
      - Edmund Cobb Charles, 42nd New York Infantry
      - Patrick J. Downing, 42nd New York Infantry
    - Card No. 17, (4 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 505)
      - T. L. Alexander, 5th United States Infantry
      - John B. S. Todd, 6th United States Infantry
      - Washington Seawell, 6th United States Infantry
      - Hannibal Day, 6th United States Infantry
    - Card No. 18, (5 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 506)
      - DeWitt Littlejohn, 110th New York Infantry
      - Clinton Dugald McDougall, 111th New York Infantry
      - George Maltby Love, 116th New York Infantry
      - George F. Nichols, 118th New York Infantry
      - Elias Peissner, 119th New York Infantry
    - Card No. 19, (4 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 507)
      - Frank C. Valee, 82nd Pennsylvania Infantry
      - Samuel Millard Bowman, 84th Pennsylvania Infantry
      - John B. Laidley, 85th Pennsylvania Infantry
      - William Kopp, 82nd Pennsylvania Infantry
    - Card No. 20, (4 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 508)
      - Henry C. Loomis, 154th New York Infantry
      - Daniel B. Allen, 154th New York Infantry
      - Jacob Sharpe, 156th New York Infantry
      - James Jordan, 158th New York Infantry
    - Card No. 21, (7 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 509)
      - Exterior portrait of John Simpson Crocker, Benjamin C. Butler, and an adjutant of 93rd New York Volunteers at Antietam, Maryland
      - James M. McCarter, 93rd Pennsylvania Infantry
      - Ambrose Spencer Cassidy, 93rd Pennsylvania Infantry
      - George H. Biddle, 95th New York Infantry
      - Unidentified man
      - John P. Spofford, 97th New York Infantry
      - John O'Mahoney, 99th New York Infantry
    - Card No. 23, (4 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 510)
      - Lewis Benedict, Jr., 162nd New York Infantry
      - Alonzo Alden,169th New York Infantry
      - Clarence Buell,169th New York Infantry
      - John McConike,169th New York Infantry
    - Card No. 24, (7 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 511)
      - William H Allen, 1st New York Infantry, 1st New York Infantry
      - Abel Carter Benedict, 1st New York Infantry
      - John E. Mulford, 3rd New York Infantry
      - Frederick Winthrop, 5th New York Infantry
      - Carlisle Boyd, 5th New York Infantry
      - Joseph S. York, 5th New York Infantry
      - Chaplain Gordon Winslow, 5th New York Infantry
    - Card No. 25, (8 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 512)
      - Albert G. Enos, 8th Pennsylvania Cavalry
      - Pennock Huey, 8th Pennsylvania Cavalry
      - Noah M. Runyan, 11th Pennsylvania Cavalry
      - Franklin A. Stratton, 11th Pennsylvania Cavalry
      - George F. McCabe, 13th Pennsylvania Cavalry
      - Marcus Albert Reno, 12th Pennsylvania Cavalry, (2 photographic prints)
      - Thomas Gibson, 14th Pennsylvania Cavalry
    - Card No. 26, (7 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 513)
      - Francis Voltaire Randall, 17th Vermont Infantry
      - Andrew C. Brown, 13th Vermont Infantry
      - Asa Peabody Blunt, 12th Vermont Infantry
      - Charles F. Spaulding, 15th Vermont Infantry
      - Roswell Farnham, 12th Vermont Infantry
      - Carlton Pennington Frost, 15th Vermont Infantry
      - Charles Cummings, 17th Vermont Infantry
    - Card No. 27, (5 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 514)
      - Rush Christopher Hawkins, 9th New York Infantry
      - James Fairman, 9th New York Infantry
      - George F. Betts, 9th New York Infantry
      - Edgar A. Kimball, 9th New York Infantry
      - Robert McKechnie, 9th New York Infantry
    - Card No. 30, (4 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 515)
      - Henry F. Martin, 31st Pennsylvania Infantry
      - Jacob G. Frick, 27th Pennsylvania Infantry
      - Joseph E. Shreve, 132nd Pennsylvania Infantry
      - Vincent M. Wilcox, 132nd Pennsylvania Infantry
    - Card No. 34, (6 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 516)
      - W. M. Wallace, 8th United States Infantry
      - John Garland, 8th United States Infantry
      - W. J. Worth, 8th United States Infantry
      - E. Pollock, 9th United States Infantry
      - W. H. Sidell, 10th United States Infantry
      - G. W. Vanderbilt, 10th United States Infantry
    - Card No. 35, (5 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 517)
      - Samuel McCartney Jackson, 40th Pennsylvania Infantry
      - Hugh Watson McNeil, 42nd Pennsylvania Infantry
      - Thomas Leiper Kane, 42nd Pennsylvania Infantry
      - John Irwin Curtin, 45th Pennsylvania Infantry
      - James L. Selfridge, 46th Pennsylvania Infantry
    - Card No. 36, (5 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 518)
      - William Wilson, 6th New York Infantry
      - William Newby, 6th New York Infantry
      - Adolphus D'Orville, 6th New York Infantry
      - Philo C. Pease, 6th New York Infantry
      - Max Kron, 8th New York Infantry
    - Card No. 38, (5 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 519)
      - Edward Dickinson Baker, 71st Pennsylvania Infantry
      - John A. Koltes, 73rd Pennsylvania Infantry
      - Henry Bohlen, 75th Pennsylvania Infantry
      - Francis Mahler, 75th Pennsylvania Infantry
    - Card No. 39, (5 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 520)
      - Hiram Berdan, 1st United States Sharpshooters
      - William Young Warren Ripley, 1st United States Sharpshooters
      - Henry A. V. Post, 2nd United States Sharpshooters
      - Homer R. Stoughton, 2nd United States Sharpshooters
      - L. C. Parmalee, 2nd United States Sharpshooters
    - Card No. 40, (7 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 521)
      - Cornelius D. Westbrook, 120th New York Infantry
      - Egbert Olcott, 121st New York Infantry
      - Archibald L. McDougall, 123rd New York Infantry
      - Augustus Van Horne Ellis, 124th New York Infantry
      - Francis M. Cummings, 124th New York Infantry
      - George L. Willard, 125th New York Infantry
    - Card No. 43, (5 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 522)
      - George F. Smith, 61st Pennsylvania Infantry
      - Jacob Bowman Sweitzer, 62nd Pennsylvania Infantry
      - Alexander Hays, 63rd Pennsylvania Infantry
      - Surgeon William H, Worthington, 63rd Pennsylvania Infantry
      - James O'Reilly, 69th Pennsylvania Infantry
    - Rufus Robinson Dawes, 6th Wisconsin Infantry (Box 10, Folder 523)
    - Virginia, Arlington. 4th Michigan Infantry in camp, (12 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 524-525)
    - Virginia, City Point, (3 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 526)
    - Virginia, City Point. Docks on James River, (6 photographic prints) (Box 10, Folder 527)
  - Oversize, Single Photographic Prints Mounted on Blue Board, (37 photographic prints)
    Albumen photographic prints created by photographers employed by the studio of Mathew B. Brady mounted on blue cardboard of images that primarily depict locations, persons, and events of the American Civil War, circa 1860-1865.
    Arranged alphabetically by geographical location of the subject. Portraits are arranged alphabetically of the surname of the subject.
    - District of Columbia, Washington
      - Cannon and guns (Box 11, Folder 528)
      - Fort Stevens. 3rd Regiment Massachusetts Heavy Artillery, Company F (Box 11, Folder 529)
      - Fort Totten. 3rd Massachusetts Heavy Artillery, officers of Companies A and B (Box 11, Folder 530)
      - Fort Totten. 3rd Massachusetts Heavy Artillery, sergeants with gun and caisson (Box 11, Folder 531)
      - Tennessee, Memphis. 1st Missouri Artillery, Battery G (Box 11, Folder 532)
      - Virginia, Broadway Landing. Pontoon bridge across the Appomattox River (Box 11, Folder 533-534)
      - Virginia, Camp Cass. 9th Massachusetts Infantry, officers (Box 11, Folder 535)
      - Virginia, Camp Jameson. 2nd Maine Infantry (Box 11, Folder 536)
      - Virginia, City Point
        - Army transport ships and store vessels on the James River (Box 11, Folder 537)
        - Building wharves (Box 11, Folder 538)
        - Stables (Box 11, Folder 539)
      - Virginia, Fort Richardson. 1st Connecticut Heavy Infantry (Box 11, Folder 540)
      - Virginia, Petersburg
        - 1st Massachusetts Cavalry, Company C (Box 11, Folder 541)
        - 1st Massachusetts Cavalry, Company D (Box 11, Folder 542)
        - 28th Massachusetts Infantry, officers (Box 11, Folder 543)
        - 3rd Indiana Cavalry, detachment (Box 11, Folder 544)
        - Overview and panorama, (4 photographic prints) (Box 11, Folder 545)
        - United States Repair Shops (Box 11, Folder 546)
      - Virginia, Petersburg, vicinity
        - Aqueduct on South Side Railroad (Box 11, Folder 547)
        - Johnson Mill on the Appomattox River (Box 11, Folder 548)
        - South Side Railroad trestle across Indian Town creek (Box 11, Folder 549)
        - Streets (Box 11, Folder 550)
      - Unidentified locations
        - 10th Massachusetts Battery, Lieutenants (Box 11, Folder 551)
        - 21st Michigan Infantry (Box 11, Folder 552)
        - 21st Michigan Infantry, Company D (Box 11, Folder 553)
        - 31st Maine Infantry, Company D (Box 11, Folder 554)
        - 34th Massachusetts Infantry (Box 11, Folder 555)
        - 44th Indiana Infantry, Company H (Box 11, Folder 556-557)
        - 44th Indiana Infantry, unidentified company (Box 11, Folder 558-559)
        - 9th Indiana Infantry, Company C (Box 11, Folder 560)
      - Studio Portrait. William Mahone, Confederate States of America (Box 11, Folder 561)
  - Oversize, Single Photographic Prints Mounted on Black Board, (6 photographic prints)
    Albumen photographic prints created by photographers employed by the studio of Mathew B. Brady mounted on black cardboard of images that primarily depict locations, persons, and events of the American Civil War, circa 1860-1865.
    - District of Columbia, Washington. Giesborough Point. Cavalry depot (Box 12, Folder 562)
    - Tennessee, Chattanooga. Headquarters and the staff of Joseph Hooker (Box 12, Folder 563)
    - Virginia, City Point. United States Military Railroad (Box 12, Folder 564)
    - Virginia, Culpeper. Group at tent and wagon of the New York Herald (Box 12, Folder 565)
    - Virginia, Warrenton. Railroad Depot (Box 12, Folder 566)
    - Unidentified location. Union saw mill (Box 12, Folder 567)
  - Oversize, Photographic Prints Mounted on Plain Board, (13 photographic prints)
    Albumen photographic prints created by photographers employed by the studio of Mathew B. Brady mounted on cardboard of images that primarily depict locations, persons, and events of the American Civil War, circa 1860-1865.
    - District of Columbia, Washington
      - Campbell Hospital (Box 13, Folder 568)
      - F Street NW and 20th Street NW, and exterior portrait of William Hoffman, the Commissary General of Prisoners, is on the right (Box 13, Folder 569)
      - Snow-covered street (Box 13, Folder 570)
    - Virginia, Alexandria
      - Barricades (Box 13, Folder 571)
      - Parade and camp of the 44th New York Infantry (Box 13, Folder 572)
    - Virginia, Arlington, Fort Richardson
      - 1st Connecticut Heavy Infantry, officers (Box 13, Folder 573)
      - Camp of Confederate prisoners (Box 13, Folder 574)
    - Virginia, Brandy Station. Exterior portrait of George Gordon Meade and his staff (Box 13, Folder 575)
    - Virginia, Falmouth, vicinity. Constructing barracks for the winter quarters (Box 13, Folder 576)
    - Virginia, Fredericksburg, Mayre's Heights. Confederate caisson and eight horses destroyed by a shell from 2nd Massachusetts artillery (Box 13, Folder 577)
    - Virginia, Petersburg. Charles N. Hewitt, 50th New York Engineers (Box 13, Folder 578)
    - Unidentified location. Exterior portrait of Winfield Scott and his staff (Box 13, Folder 579)
    - Studio portrait. Founders of Knights of Pythias (Box 13, Folder 580)
      Identified as Justus H. Rathbone, William H. Burnett, David L. Burnett, and Edward S. Kimball
  - Oversize, Albumen Prints, Unmounted, (19 photographic prints)
    - District of Columbia, Washington
      - Exterior portrait of Winfield Scott and his staff (Box 14, Folder 581)
      - Fort DeRussy. Interior of fort with soldiers and cannon (Box 14, Folder 582)
      - Fort Lincoln. Soldiers in formation in front of camp (Box 14, Folder 583)
      - Fort Totten. Interior (Box 14, Folder 584)
      - Long Bridge over the Potomac River (Box 14, Folder 585)
        Mathew Brady standing with back to camera next to building
    - Georgia, Allatoona Pass.
      - Defenses for the Etowah River Bridge and the Nashville, Chattanooga and St. Louis Railway (Box 14, Folder 586)
      - From the Etowah River (Box 14, Folder 587)
    - Georgia, Atlanta. Confederate fortification (Box 14, Folder 588)
    - Georgia, Marietta, vicinity. Kennesaw Mountain (Box 14, Folder 589)
    - Georgia, Paulding County. Battlefield of New Hope Church (Box 14, Folder 590-591)
    - Georgia, Resaca Battlefield (Box 14, Folder 592-593)
    - Georgia, Whitfield County. Buzzard Roost, also known as Mill Creek Gap (Box 14, Folder 594)
    - Tennessee, Chattanooga Valley. From Lookout Mountain (Box 14, Folder 595)
    - Tennessee, Lookout Mountain (Box 14, Folder 596)
    - Tennessee, Lookout Mountain. Lulu Lake (Box 14, Folder 597)
    - Tennessee, Missionary Ridge. From Orchard Knob (Box 14, Folder 598)
  - Glass Photographic Negatives, Cartes-de-visite, ( 13 glass negatives)
    Studio portraits on wet collodion glass plate negatives that primarily depict officers in the United States military, politicians, and civilians.
    - Studio portraits
      - Johnson, Andrew (Box 15, Folder 599-600)
      - Nelson, Thomas Amos Rogers (Box 15, Folder 601)
      - Page, William, possibly (Box 15, Folder 602)
      - Sherman, William Tecumsah (Box 15, Folder 603)
      - Sickles, Daniel Edgar (Box 15, Folder 604)
      - Stratton, Mercy Lavinia Warren Bump (Box 15, Folder 605)
        Also known as Mrs. Tom Thumb, the wife of General Tom Thumb, Charles Sherwood Stratton
      - Taylor, Bayard (Box 15, Folder 606)
      - Group (Box 15, Folder 607)
        Identified from left to right as George Washington Morrison Nutt (Commodore Nutt), Mercy Lavinia Warren Bump Stratton, an unidentified man, and Charles Sherwood Stratton (General Tom Thumb)
      - Man (Box 15, Folder 608-611)
  - Glass Photographic Negative, Carte-de-visite strip negative, 3.5" X 7.5", (1 glass plate negative)
    - Studio portrait of a man posed standing with a cane and beard (Box 15, Folder 612)
- Levin Corbin Handy Studio, 1849-circa 1956; Series II; (28 boxes)
  This series consists of photographic prints and negatives, and a small amount of records from the studio of Levin Corbin Handy that include studio portraits and interior and exterior views of structures, buildings, and artwork primarily located in Washington, D.C. Some materials document the sale of images created by the studio of Mathew B. Brady and marketed by the studio of Levin Corbin Handy. The series also includes a small quantity of papers from the studio.
  This series is arranged first with proof books from the studio, followed by photographic prints created by the studio and images originally created by the Mathew B. Brady Studio and printed by the studio, copy photography, oversize photographic prints, then followed by glass and film photographic negatives arranged by size and medium, and then a small amount of papers.
  Proof Books
  Original Photographs
  Copy photographs
  Oversize Photographs
  Photographic Negatives
  Papers